Guide to the Robert Herrick Papers 1887-1960
University of Chicago Library
- Series X: Miscellaneous Correspondence, Interviews and Ephemera
  - Correspondence [Emory]-Herrick, Philip (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Knight, Grant-Luckie, Annie (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Marquand, John P.-Woods, Donald A. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Interviews with Philip Herrick 1953-1960 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous research notes, etc. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Key to Chimes (Box 27, Folder 8)